http://www.ielnet.org/privacy-policy

Home/
Intern in DC/Why Internships MatterHow We Help You Find InternshipsWhere You Can InternWhat You Will Be Doing
Engage in Class/Core Course in PolicyInternship Seminar
Explore Life in DC/Where You Will LiveWhat You Can See & DoStudent StoriesSocial MediaDiscovering the District
More Info/For International StudentsFor ParentsFor Internship HostsFor Faculty & AdministratorsFor AlumniAbout UsContact UsSearch
How to Apply/Apply NowImportant DatesScholarships and CostsEarning Credit
Donate/
Capitalize On Your Potential
Privacy Policy
Home/
Intern in DC/Why Internships MatterHow We Help You Find InternshipsWhere You Can InternWhat You Will Be Doing
Engage in Class/Core Course in PolicyInternship Seminar
Explore Life in DC/Where You Will LiveWhat You Can See & DoStudent StoriesSocial MediaDiscovering the District
More Info/For International StudentsFor ParentsFor Internship HostsFor Faculty & AdministratorsFor AlumniAbout UsContact UsSearch
How to Apply/Apply NowImportant DatesScholarships and CostsEarning Credit
Donate/
Privacy policyThe following policy discloses the privacy practices for the Washington Internship Institute’s website (http://www.wiidc.org)Information GatheringThe Washington Internship Institute maintains log files of all access to its site for the purposes of site management. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser version, referrer, operating system, and date/time stamp. These logs are used to administer the site, track the user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.Information Provided VoluntarilyWhile using the Washington Internship Institute's website, you may choose to provide information to us through online forms, email or other electronic means. Any personally-identifiable information you submit will be used by the Washington Internship Institute only for the purpose(s) indicated. Requests for information will be directed to the appropriate staff to respond to the request, and may be recorded to help us improve our site to better respond to similar requests. Online applications and other materials submitted by applicants and admitted students via WII Link will be used for program-related purposes including our admissions process, the internship placement process, our classes, and housing arrangements.Information UseThe Washington Internship Institute uses the information described above to help us improve our website, to respond to your inquiries, and to deliver program services. We will not sell, trade, or rent this information. In certain instances, in order to provide information and services, or as required by law, the Washington Internship Institute may disseminate non-personally and personally-identifiable information to third parties. In these instances, the information provided to the third party shall be limited to the extent necessary to provide the user-requested information and/or services, or as required by applicable law enforcement agencies.Opt OutThe Washington Internship Institute respects your privacy and does not want to contact you unless you indicate to us that you want to be contacted by us. If you choose to join our email list, you may opt out at any time by clicking the appropriate link in an email you receive. Or email us at info@wiidc.org, ask to be removed from the email list, and provide your full name. To opt out of other communication, please email us at info@wiidc.org and provide the details of your request along with your full name.CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Cookies will only be enabled when users acknowledge the banner notifying them of the use of cookies. We use only session cookies to make navigation of the site easier.Links to Other SitesSome webpages may include links to sites external to the Washington Internship Institute. The Washington Internship Institute is not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.Notification of ChangesThe Washington Internship Institute reserves the right, at its discretion, to make changes to this policy at any time. Please check this privacy policy webpage periodically for updates.Contact InformationIf you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at info@wiidc.org.
1825 K St. NW, Suite 705, Washington, DC 20006(202) 833-8580 / (800) 435-0770Privacy Policy
